CHRISTIAN DELICAAT

△ httr

https://itschris.dev/

cdelicaat.me@gmail.com

(+31) 6 169 18 278

Spijkenisse, Netherlands

ំ្រ linkedin.com/in/christiandelicaat/

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm Chris — a gameplay & tools programming student and proceduralism enthusiast. I've always wanted to make games, but didn't know where to start. I ended up studying application development, thinking it would include game development — it didn't. After graduating, I worked in web development for a few years, but the lack of creativity drained me. I eventually quit, invested a year into self-study, and committed fully to game development. Now, I'm a third-year student at BUas, doing what I actually love.

EDUCATION

BSc • Creative Media and Game Technologies

Breda University of Applied Sciences | Breda, Netherlands

2022 - Present

Secondary vocational education Lv.4 • Application Development

ROC Da Vinci I Dordrecht, Netherlands

2015 - 2018

High School Diploma

Thorbecke Lyceum I Rotterdam, Netherlands

2010 - 2015

SKILLS

Full-stack Web Development

IntelliJ IDEs (PHPStorm, Rider, Android Studio)

 $\mathbb{C}++$

Unreal Engine

Perforce Git

Figma Premake

Visual Studio Atlassian Software

STRONG POINTS

Clear communication Team collaboration

Quality-focused Strong Leadership

Fast learner Problem solving

Reliable Organized

Adaptable Initiative

Translates tech into plain language

LANGUAGES

Dutch - Native

English - Proficient

INTERESTS

Gaming Cooking

Brewing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Inventeers | Leiden

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

2022/01 - 2022/08

Collaborated with a small team to develop and integrate new IoT features and troubleshoot reported issues.

SELF-STUDY IN GAME DEVELOPMENT

2021 - 2022

CAK Groep | Dordrecht

BACKEND PHP DEVELOPER

2019/09 - 2021/01

Collaboration with a small team to implement new features. Finding and fixing reported bugs as well as documenting the findings. Writing tests for new and existing classes and features.

Ridemi | The Hague

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

2018/06 - 2018/09

INTERN FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

2018/02 - 2018/06

Reviewing code, debugging problems and correcting issues. Training and supervising interns for ongoing projects. Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery and developed user-oriented visuals and features using front-end languages to speed up productivity.

Jermaine Art | Rotterdam

INTERN FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

2016/09 - 2017/02

Designed, build and maintained Wordpress sites using scripting languages, content-creating tools, management tools and digital media.